Just give me 9 minutes.
9 minutes?
So, in this section,
I found the problem
that when you scroll up,
you can see both the zeroes.
And you don't know if the website is broken
or not.
So, if you have seen one zero,
or if you have seen the first zero,
zero commissions, and then the next zero
and zero bias,
and then the next sentence,
that would be better. Or if there is
nothing to show, you can explore.
Somewhere,
when I read the word commissions,
I feel,
instantly as a consumer,
I don't know which commission
I am talking about.
I am talking about the commission
that is taken from me. Which commission is this?
But okay, when I thought,
okay, the website
that is taken from the bank is talking about commission.
But okay.
Now, the website that is taken from the bank,
this is the context that I am going to
cover. And I am saying, zero bias.
So, which is the bias
that is taken from the website and the bank?
Then I feel, no, no, zero bias
means, this is not going to
push any bank.
So, I have to switch
What does this do? It doesn't make it easy
to understand.
Somewhere, it should be said
that either
this whole section is
about website and bank,
or this whole section is about
website and customer.
It should not be mixed
in the context.
So, there are
two things. So, you get a fair
view of every lender listed on a platform
with non-ranked or pushed
of another. So, we have to say
that
we
don't take commission
or we don't take any money
from the bank.
So, we don't have any bias
to push the bank forward.
The ranking we have
is actually
the ranking of customer benefit.
The ranking is such that
the bank is the one
that gets the most benefit
from the customer.
And no one can change our ranking
and give us money.
In the last
sentence, we have to say this.
But what I feel
is that every lender
listed on a platform
might have better wording.
So, something like you get a
fair view of all lenders
in the market,
ranked
fairly.
Or basically
this sentence,
the size of this sentence is very small.
So, what we have to say is
that fair view of every lender
and
no one's ranking
has been changed or no one has been
pushed forward.
That means no one has been pushed forward.
So, fair view
of lenders
and no one has been pushed forward.
There is such a gist.
At least in Shraddhan,
in polished English, we have to
convey this gist.
We have to convey this.
We have used polished English.
Normal users will understand.
Yes, polished English
means
we have to understand it
but something like
96% or 98% conversation
can be done
in just 300 words
in English.
We don't have to use
those big words.
We have to understand
Best of all, you can look
through everything at your pace
without spam calls, hard sell or push notifications.
So,
I want to ask you
what is the significance of these three things?
What is the difference between these three things?
Spam call, hard sell. How is hard sell different?
Hard sell.
You didn't send the documents.
They are hard sell.
Push notifications
means on WhatsApp
it is pre-uploaded
Spam calls
are unnecessary calls.
Spam call and hard sell
are a bit intersected.
Spam call is basically
where we sell our data
and those people
call them.
Basically,
what we have to say from this section
is that we don't make any
urgency
for any thing.
We will bring you everything
and you can do things at your pace.
You won't get unnecessary calls
or you won't have to
sell anything.
We won't send you notifications
asking you to buy or sell.
We will bring you everything
and you can do it at your pace.
Now,
I have a concern
that
these four sections
do we need
these four sections?
Can we
trim some of these sections?
Now,
this section
basically,
so many people
have read this text.
In some forms,
if we can show
this journey of
we completely re-engineered
this home-run journey.
We have to keep a title
and in that part, we have to show
three sections.
In one section,
the market is such that
you can do a cross-examination.
This information is unique.
The hope is
to make the first section
much bigger.
Basically,
what is the total unique information?
Re-engineered or home-run,
this is the title.
This is the
comparability of the market.
This is the unique information.
You can see
without knowing
without giving up your information.
Basically,
we make you
powerful
or knowledgeable
without taking anything
in back, anything in return.
And we
make it easy for you.
And we flip the game
that you
or the bank completes it for you.
This is actually
not a team point.
This is not a team point.
This is made comparable.
You can take
And then you apply
and then complete it.
We have
standardized everything
and put it in one section.
You can
take it completely
and see.
You don't give any information.
And when you get it
in one shot
you give it to everyone
and the bank will
complete it for your business.
This is definitely a coherent story.
But the word
or the sentence formation
is not that coherent.